<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Society of Software Engineers</title><description>Input students, export engineers</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Society of Software Engineers</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 1.20</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:46:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Welcome to the New SSE Website</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm glad you're here! We have some amazing stuff going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past year, MSOE's Society of Software Engineers has been busy working on updating their website to make it more flexible, informative, and open. One of the biggest motivators behind this movement is to allow student members of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2018/01/12/new-sse-website/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5a598982f3737ea32c806be7</guid><category>information</category><dc:creator>Hunter Parks</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 04:22:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/01/finn-hackshaw-131930.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2018/01/finn-hackshaw-131930.jpg" alt="Welcome to the New SSE Website"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm glad you're here! We have some amazing stuff going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past year, MSOE's Society of Software Engineers has been busy working on updating their website to make it more flexible, informative, and open. One of the biggest motivators behind this movement is to allow student members of SSE to actively participate in the development and maintenance of this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally, the official SSE website was going to be created using &lt;a href="https://angular.io/"&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt;. As time went on, it was clear that the open source blogging platform &lt;a href="https://ghost.org/"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt; might be a better choice for SSE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="whatisghost"&gt;What is Ghost?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost is a fully open source, hackable platform for building and running a modern online publication. We power blogs, magazines and journalists from Zappos to Sky News.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other terms, Ghost is a publication platform that can be leveraged to accomplish many different site goals - and it is open source! This means that SSE can use the platform to build an engaging, informative, and custom website that can be programmed by the students of SSE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="whatisinitforme"&gt;What is in it for me?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an SSE member, this website will your hub for all things SSE. From this site you will be able to see calendar events, interesting articles in the world of technology and engineering, and participate in discussion with fellow SSE members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="canihelp"&gt;Can I help?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course! The purpose of this website is to allow students to grow and learn in their programming skills. While some knowledge of &lt;a href="https://www.w3.org/html/"&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.w3.org/Style/CSS/"&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/JavaScript"&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt; can come in handy, no prior knowledge is required - we would love to teach you! All SSE website source code and content is available on our &lt;a href="https://github.com/msoe-sse/"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; repository.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photo Credit: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/@finnhackshaw"&gt;Finn Hackshaw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>